You're back Sister
Looks like Fu Chenzhou doesn't treat you that well either
At least he didn't make me
sign an annulment at the wedding reception
Enough I called you back today
not for you to keep arguing
Then it is to make me apologize
I won't sign
The video has already been leaked
It affects both families
Don't just act for momentary satisfaction
For the sake of your partnership
I should admit my mistakes
and apologize deeply
What should I apologize for
If you think I'm wrong
I can apologize
But everyone online is questioning Brother Chengze
That was no misunderstanding
It was the truth being exposed
Sister Mom and Dad
never felt you owed anyone
Then take off the ring
Don't drag Yurong into this
She's not involved
Last night she wore my
wedding ring on stage
Today she sits here saying it's a misunderstanding
Since she's involved every time
she's no bystander
Su Mingyao I'm asking you one last time
Will you delete it or not